

About Me

Full Stack Web Developer.

Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic and static web projects. Well-versed in numerous Technologies including HTML5, PHP OOP,

JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skills

Bootstrap 4
Responsive Webdesign
JavaScript
Php
Codignitor 3
Seo friendly

Education

2018 - 2020

Master's Degree, MCA (Distances) Integral University ,Lucknow

2014 - 2017

Bechalor's Degree, BCA Integral Univerity,Lucknow

2013 - 2014

Class XII (I.S.C Board), Brain's Convent College, Lucknow

2011 - 2012

Class X (I.C.S.E Board), Brain's Convent College, Lucknow

Arbab Hussain

Full Stack Developer



+91 8853529480

arbabh411@gmail.com

289/24b Moti Nagar, Lucknow. 226004

Experience

Sept 2019- Current- Digihive (Full Stack Developer)

- Develop new digital assets as identified by supervisor and management
- Modify existing code to accommodate client needs including changing in ui/ux, add new feature to admin panel or the frontend, maintaining server, and other development tasks
- Ensure all your work is performed according to the brief and the minimum requirements for each client
- Develop fast and efficiently to meet tight deadlines
 Update and amend existing assets
- Maintain client digital assets to the best of your ability using clean, accessible mark-up according to the latest web standards
- Help and advise project managers with client's digital requests
- Keep an eye on the latest trends to help boost development efficiencies

Sept 2018- Aug 2019- Dr. Aziz Khan (Developer and Multimedia Manager)

- Collaborate with designers to implement the graphical design to UI/UX
- Ensuring the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs
- Modifying existing templates for clients needs maintain mobile friendly layout

May 2018 - Aug 2018 - Freelancer

- Developed front end website architecture
- Developed back end website applications
- Ensuring cross-platform optimization for mobile phones
- Maintain quality and ensure the responsiveness of applications

Oct 2017- April 2018- Moody Inks (Developer and Marketing)

- Developed front end website architecture
- Designed user interactions on web pages